mindset.co.za 2011-11-06

# Privacy Policy | Mindset Network

Your privacy is important to Mindset Network.  This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Mindset Network collects, and the ways in which Mindset Network uses that personal information.

#### Personal information collection

Mindset Network may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * information about your use of this website (including your operating system and browser type, your geographical location and the pages you have visited);
  * information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website (including your name and surname);
  * information about transactions carried out over this website (including your subscription to the Mindset Newsletter);
  * information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services (including your email address for the purposes of subscribing to the Mindset Newsletter; and
  * any other information that you send to Mindset Network.

#### Using personal information

Mindset Network may use your personal information to:

  * administer this website;personalize the website for you;
  * enable your access to and use of the website services;
  * supply to you services that you subscribe to;
  * process and monies you donate to Mindset Network and provide you with tax certification;
  * send you marketing communications from time to time.

Where Mindset Network discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Mindset Network may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

#### Securing your data

Mindset Network will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

Mindset Network will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.

Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.

#### Cross-border data transfers

Information that Mindset Network collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which Mindset Network operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website, especially in the discussion forums, will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

#### Updating this statement

Mindset Network may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

#### Other websites

This website contains links to other websites.

Mindset Network is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

#### Contact Mindset Network

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or Mindset Network’s treatment of your personal information, please write to

#### This privacy statement

This privacy statement is based on a precedent created by employmentlawcontracts.co.uk and published by freenetlaw.com.
